[{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664064384,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":13832,"timeElapsed":83994},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664078560,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":14173,"timeElapsed":98170},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664090548,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":11986,"timeElapsed":110158},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664095383,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":4833,"timeElapsed":114993},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664103703,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":8318,"timeElapsed":123313},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664107071,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":3365,"timeElapsed":126681},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664111569,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":4495,"timeElapsed":131178},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664122619,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":11048,"timeElapsed":142229},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664126583,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":3962,"timeElapsed":146192},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664152426,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":24158,"timeElapsed":172036},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664155301,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":2871,"timeElapsed":174911},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664161530,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":6224,"timeElapsed":181140},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664170181,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":8646,"timeElapsed":189791},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664174602,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4418,"timeElapsed":194212},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664178149,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":3545,"timeElapsed":197759},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664181713,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3562,"timeElapsed":201323},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664184492,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":2777,"timeElapsed":204102},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664186807,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2313,"timeElapsed":206417},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664197465,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":9123,"timeElapsed":217075},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664199843,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2377,"timeElapsed":219453},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664206186,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":6340,"timeElapsed":225796},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664208478,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2290,"timeElapsed":228088},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664213055,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":4574,"timeElapsed":232665},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664217185,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":4129,"timeElapsed":236795},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664221273,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4085,"timeElapsed":240883},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664224860,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3585,"timeElapsed":244470},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664228282,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3421,"timeElapsed":247892},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664239666,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":10319,"timeElapsed":259276},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664241673,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2005,"timeElapsed":261283},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664250328,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":8654,"timeElapsed":269938},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664252361,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2031,"timeElapsed":271971},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664258589,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":6226,"timeElapsed":278199},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664261913,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":3321,"timeElapsed":281523},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664266599,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4684,"timeElapsed":286209},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664268962,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2361,"timeElapsed":288572},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664274076,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":5112,"timeElapsed":293686},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664284220,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":6353,"timeElapsed":303830},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664286967,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":2744,"timeElapsed":306577},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664292257,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":5288,"timeElapsed":311867},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664294417,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2158,"timeElapsed":314026},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664297613,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3195,"timeElapsed":317223},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664299672,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2057,"timeElapsed":319282},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664302153,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2479,"timeElapsed":321763},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664304402,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2247,"timeElapsed":324011},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664306011,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":1607,"timeElapsed":325621},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664312170,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5286,"timeElapsed":331780},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664314627,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2456,"timeElapsed":334237},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664317853,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3224,"timeElapsed":337463},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664319753,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1898,"timeElapsed":339363},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664324253,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4498,"timeElapsed":343863},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664326386,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2131,"timeElapsed":345996},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664328462,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2074,"timeElapsed":348072},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664332159,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3695,"timeElapsed":351769},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664335505,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3344,"timeElapsed":355115},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664344258,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":8751,"timeElapsed":363868},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664367548,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":21553,"timeElapsed":387158},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664372007,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":4457,"timeElapsed":391617},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664380238,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":8228,"timeElapsed":399848},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664382291,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2051,"timeElapsed":401900},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664398024,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":15731,"timeElapsed":417634},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664400802,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2776,"timeElapsed":420412},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664406663,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":5859,"timeElapsed":426273},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664411004,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":4339,"timeElapsed":430614},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664414042,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3036,"timeElapsed":433652},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664418462,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4417,"timeElapsed":438072},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664425102,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5490,"timeElapsed":444712},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664428494,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3389,"timeElapsed":448104},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664431100,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2604,"timeElapsed":450710},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664434106,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3004,"timeElapsed":453716},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664436929,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2820,"timeElapsed":456539},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664440084,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3153,"timeElapsed":459693},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664442914,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2828,"timeElapsed":462524},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664445590,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2675,"timeElapsed":465200},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664448027,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2436,"timeElapsed":467637},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664528615,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":78732,"timeElapsed":548225},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664531841,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3224,"timeElapsed":551451},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664541096,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":9253,"timeElapsed":560705},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664543091,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":1993,"timeElapsed":562701},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664548255,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5162,"timeElapsed":567865},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664550484,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2228,"timeElapsed":570094},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664553366,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2879,"timeElapsed":572976},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664555729,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2362,"timeElapsed":575339},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664557441,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":1710,"timeElapsed":577051},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664568620,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":9401,"timeElapsed":588230},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664570795,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2174,"timeElapsed":590405},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664573811,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3014,"timeElapsed":593421},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664577017,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3205,"timeElapsed":596627},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664578971,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":1952,"timeElapsed":598581},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664580800,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":1827,"timeElapsed":600410},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664583832,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3030,"timeElapsed":603442},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664586154,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2321,"timeElapsed":605764},{"subjectID":"d7qb6lr9wd","prolificID":"6658d57e96aa5518f7414d69","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421629ca0db6f8b78d1e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664588243,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2087,"timeElapsed":607853}]